Sander van 't Noordende

Group Chief Executive Products at Accenture

Experience

Group Chief Executive Products Operating Group at Accenture

January 2014 - Present (3 years 3 months)

Group chief executive of Products at Accenture, which serves clients in the consumer goods & services, retail, life sciences, travel, industrial equipment & automotive industries.

I am a member of Accenture's Global Management Committee.

Board Member at Avanade

April 2015 - Present (2 years)

Board Member at Out and Equal

2016 - Present (1 year)

Out & Equal Workplace Advocates is the world's premier nonprofit organization dedicated to achieving lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender workplace equality.

Group Chief Executive Management Consulting at Accenture

March 2011 - December 2013 (2 years 10 months)

Leading Accenture's Global Management Consulting Practice

Group Chief Executive Resources at Accenture

September 2006 - February 2011 (4 years 6 months)

Leading Accenture's business in Resources Industries (Energy, Chemicals, Natural Resources, Utilities)

Client Service Group Managing Partner at Accenture

September 2003 - September 2006 (3 years 1 month)

Leading Accenture's Resources Operating Group in France, Netherlands, Belgium. In 2005-2006 Latin America, Africa and Souther Europe were added to my responsibilities.

Country Managing Director The Netherlands at Accenture

September 2001 - September 2006 (5 years 1 month)

Overseeing Accenture's activities in the Dutch market

Partner at Accenture

September 1999 - September 2001 (2 years 1 month)

Leading the Dutch Utilities Practice of Accenture

Strategy Consultant at Accenture

October 1987 - September 1999 (12 years)

I started my career as a Strategy Consultant in the Financial Services and Utilities Industries. Progressed from Business Analyst to Partner over this period.

Summary

Global business leader in professional services: strategy, consulting, digital, technology and operations.

Group chief executive of Products at Accenture, which serves clients in the consumer goods & services, retail, life sciences, travel, industrial equipment & automotive industries.

I am a member of Accenture's Global Management Committee. I am a Board member at Avanade, a joint venture between Microsoft and Accenture.

Joined Accenture in October 1987

Skills & Expertise

Strategy

Management Consulting

Outsourcing

Business Development

Management

CRM

Leadership

Consulting

Enterprise Software

Energy

Finance

Sustainability

Business Transformation

Change Management

Business Strategy

Business Process Improvement

Business Analysis

Program Management

Project Management

Business Process

IT Strategy

Business Intelligence

Professional Services

Strategic Planning

Executive Management

ERP

Integration

Governance

Mergers & Acquisitions

Education

Eindhoven University of Technology

Bedrijfskunde - Industrial Engineering, Marketing, Finance, 1981 - 1987 Activities and Societies: Eindhovens Studenten Corps, Aleph, EMHC

Interests

General economic and business developments, enjoying the arts: opera - musical - modern art, sports: fieldhockey - European Hockey League -

Sander van 't Noordende

Group Chief Executive Products at Accenture



Contact Sander on LinkedIn